

Lisboa, Portugal +351 912 031 867 scralowrealow@gmail.com https://anadebarros.github.io

## BIOGRAPHY

I'm a 33 year old web developer from Lisbon. Avid self-learner, curiosity and passion are my main driving forces to keep improving everyday. Web development has allowed me to expand my creativity while at the same time applying all of the logic and precision I have come to develop as a researcher. I love pushing my own limits and challenge myself everyday. I excel in creative team environments.



https://github.com/anadebarros



in ana-de-barros-4750998

# EXPERIENCE

#### COMMUNICATION OFFICER

iMM Lisboa, 2016 - Present

Responsible for restructuring and leading the communication unit. Developed new digital strategy.

#### Managing Scientific Editor

BioNews Services, 2015-2016

Digital edition of science articles in Wordpress for 18 different websites.

### Managing Scientific Writer

BioNews Services, 2014-2015

Scientific writing in several research topics.

# Post Doc Researcher

iMM Lisboa, 2013-2014

Research in immunology and breast cancer.

# **EDUCATION**

#### WEB AND MOBILE DEVELOPMENT

FLAG Lisboa, 2016 - Present

Learned about website and web app development, front-end and back-end & Android/iOS development.

## PHD IMMUNOLOGY

University of Lisbon, 2007 - 2011

PhD thesis on the role of CD27 in gamma-delta T cell development.

### MSc Biomolecular Archaeology

University of Manchester, 2005 -

MSc thesis on quantitative real-time PCR for ancient DNA amplification.

# PHD IMMUNOLOGY

University of Lisbon, 2007 - 2011

PhD thesis on the role of CD27 in gamma-delta T cell development.

# **CURRENTLY WORKING ON...**

Web app built with PHP, Javascript, Using MySQL as database. Making HTTP requests to Twitter and Google Maps APIs to display user feed and geographical location.

## **SKILLS**

HTML5 /CSS3	_
Javascript	_
MySQL	
PHP	
Python	
Bootstrap	_